so you can control remotely.
You can move your head around to get a sense of depth.
You can lower it, you can go higher,
which is what you can't do with a 2D camera.
And here we have an arm in Singapore,
and I can lift it and control it remotely.
And what it'll let me do is if I want to pick up,
say, this pink cube, I can look to the left
and line up the claw so that it's lined up
with a pink cube, whereas here it would be harder to tell.
But now I'm absolutely certain because I can look around.
So now if I close the claw,
I can easily pick up the pink cube.
Once we have the pink cube,
then I can pick it up and I can look around.
I can look to the side and see that there is in fact,
space over the hole.
And once I have it lined up on both fronts,
I can just let go and boom.
We now have the pink cube inside the cup.